# Greg Field

## **Summary**

A Computer Science Graduate with 1 years experience in Business Process Automation. Proficient in several programming languages with a solid understanding of the Software Development Life Cycle. Personally interested in Web Development, specifically using a Vue.js, Express and Mongo Stack.

#### Education

2018 – 2019 Sept Modules

2018 – 2019 Sept MSc. Computer Science, *University of Birmingham*, Birmingham.

- Introduction to Computer Science
- Software Workshop (Java)
- Databases (Postgres)
- Data Structures & Algorithms
- Software Engineering 1 & 2
- Introduction to Artificial Intelligence
- Operating Systems & Networks
- Introduction to Human Computer Interaction
- Summer Project (Python, Librosa)

2013 – 2016 **BSc. Music Technology**, *University of the West of England*, Bristol, *2:2*. Modules

- Introductory Audio Programming (C++)
- Game Audio Programming (FMod)
- Software Development for Audio (C++)
- Mobile & Physical Computing

#### Technical skills

Computer Languages JavaScript, Java, Python, C++

Web Dev Vue.js, HTML, SCSS, CSS3, Node, Express

Web Tools REST, XML

LowCode Mendix

Database Postgres, MongoDB

Software & Tools LaTex

Version Control GIT

#### Experience

2019 - Present Graduate Software Developer, AuraQ, Great Malvern.

2018 – 2018 Packing Assistant, Coles Puddings, Saffron Walden.

2018 – 2018 Kitchen Assistant, AristoCaters, Sawston.

2017 – 2018 Team Member, Krispy Kreme, Cambridge.

2016 - 2017 Catering Assistant, John Lewis, Cambridge.

### Interests

 $Music \quad I \ enjoy \ writing \ and \ playing \ music \ in \ my \ spare \ time, \ I \ can \ play \ the \ piano, \ guitar \ and \ drums.$ 

Coding Recently I have been learning some web development focused on using Vue.js, Express and MongoDB. I also enjoy solving coding challenges on sites such as hackerrank.com